<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on OptimuSoft</title>
    <link>http://127.0.0.1:1313/optimuSoft/en/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on OptimuSoft</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 11:58:39 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://127.0.0.1:1313/optimuSoft/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hipster Ipsum</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1313/optimuSoft/en/blog/hipster-ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 11:58:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1313/optimuSoft/en/blog/hipster-ipsum/</guid>
      <description>Occupy mlkshk kale chips woke, listicle locavore next level fingerstache glossier aesthetic man braid before they sold out kitsch prism. Cred copper mug freegan, flannel YOLO single-origin coffee skateboard artisan four loko church-key man bun. Synth literally gastropub, kombucha chillwave helvetica offal truffaut church-key freegan pop-up gentrify narwhal. Kombucha viral vexillologist green juice. Slow-carb hoodie mumblecore tumeric tattooed meditation, lo-fi fap cred affogato forage whatever austin. Shabby chic direct trade migas, brunch gochujang sriracha chambray fanny pack 8-bit mustache letterpress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Ipsum</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1313/optimuSoft/en/blog/startup-ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 12:04:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1313/optimuSoft/en/blog/startup-ipsum/</guid>
      <description>SpaceTeam affordances quantitative vs. qualitative SpaceTeam physical computing earned media thinker-maker-doer pair programming. Bootstrapping pitch deck physical computing driven cortado human-centered design innovate human-centered design driven. Grok pitch deck fund pitch deck sticky note affordances minimum viable product integrate paradigm viral iterate. Driven fund thought leader personas workflow SpaceTeam viral pair programming physical computing intuitive 360 campaign latte bootstrapping minimum viable product. Bootstrapping physical computing responsive pitch deck SpaceTeam parallax long shadow pitch deck bootstrapping ideate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee Ipsum</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1313/optimuSoft/en/blog/coffee-ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 12:04:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1313/optimuSoft/en/blog/coffee-ipsum/</guid>
      <description>Aromatic aroma con panna, crema so coffee robust coffee barista, café au lait trifecta that strong blue mountain cortado aftertaste. Aroma extraction french press, skinny sweet, blue mountain cup roast barista, beans, extra cappuccino mug crema strong. Americano caffeine white, con panna saucer sit, con panna eu, carajillo aftertaste kopi-luwak, body aftertaste cup single origin café au lait saucer. Macchiato java sweet arabica, turkish cup, eu flavour mug extraction white cortado saucer est white brewed instant, rich, barista breve cappuccino barista organic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shortcode Tests</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1313/optimuSoft/en/blog/shortcode-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 13:39:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1313/optimuSoft/en/blog/shortcode-tests/</guid>
      <description>Hello, Thanks for downloading and testing our my shortcode pack. Below will load all of the shortcodes and display the various options they have. If you like and enjoy these short codes, please post a link on your blog to GeekThis.net, I would really appreciate it.
Installing New Shortcodes To install shortcodes, copy each HTML file relating to a shortcode you want and place it into the shortcode directory inside of Hugo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Undated post</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1313/optimuSoft/en/blog/no-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1313/optimuSoft/en/blog/no-date/</guid>
      <description>I was born yesterday, tomorrow. YOU KNOW!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>